Chase Going Woodhouse Papers 1983.0009
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Series II: Auerbach Service Bureau, undated, 1944-1981
  - Subseries D: Bureau Activities, undated, 1945-1981
    - Meetings
      - Conference Series Reports, 1959; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Meetings/Box11:21 (Box 11, Folder 21 [39153019711755])
      - Conference Series Reports, 1960; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Meetings/Box11:22 (Box 11, Folder 22 [39153019711763])
      - Conference Series Reports, 1961; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Meetings/Box12:1 (Box 12, Folder 1 [39153019711771])
      - Conference Series Reports, 1962; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Meetings/Box12:2 (Box 12, Folder 2, Folder 2 [39153019711789])
      - Conference Series Reports, 1963; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Meetings/Box12:3 (Box 12, Folder 3 [39153019711797])
      - Conference Series Reports, 1964; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Meetings/Box12:4 (Box 12, Folder 4 [39153019711805])
      - Conference Series Reports, 1965; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box12:5 (Box 12, Folder 5 [39153019711813])
      - Conference Series Reports, 1966; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Meetings/Box12:6 (Box 12, Folder 6 [39153019711821])
      - Conference Series Reports, 1967; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box12:7 (Box 12, Folder 7 [39153019711839])
        Reports; Advisory boards; Women in community organization; Woodhouse, Chase Going.
      - Conference Series Reports, 1968; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box12:8 (Box 12, Folder 8 [39153019711847])
        Reports; Women in community organization; Advisory boards; Woodhouse, Chase Going.
      - Conference Series Reports, 1969; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box12:9 (Box 12, Folder 9 [39153019711854])
      - Conference Series Reports, 1970; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box12:10 (Box 12, Folder 10 [39153019711862])
      - Conference Series Reports, 1971; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box12:11 (Box-folder 12:11)
      - Conference Series Reports, 1972; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box12:12 (Box-folder 12:12)
      - Conference Series Reports, 1973; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box12:13 (Box-folder 12:13)
      - Conference Series Reports, 1974; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box12:14 (Box-folder 12:14)
      - Conference Series Reports, 1975; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box12:15 (Box-folder 12:15)
      - Conference Series Reports, 1976; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box12:16 (Box-folder 12:16)
      - Day care, undated; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Meetings/Box12:17 (Box-folder 12:17)
      - Dinner Meetings, 1951-1952; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Meetings/Box12:18 (Box-folder 12:18)
      - Dinner Meetings, 1961; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Meetings/Box12:19 (Box-folder 12:19)
      - Dinner Meetings, 1967; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Meetings/Box12:20 (Box-folder 12:20)
      - Education, 1945-1946; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Meetings/Box12:21 (Box-folder 12:21)
      - Education, 1949-1950; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Meetings/Box12:22 (Box-folder 12:22)
      - Education: Educational Guidance Course, 1952; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Meetings/Box12:23 (Box-folder 12:23)
      - Education: Schools, 1952; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Meetings/Box12:24 (Box-folder 12:24)
      - Education, 1966; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Meetings/Box12:25 (Box-folder 12:25)
      - Education: Guidance, 1968; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Meetings/Box12:26 (Box-folder 12:26)
      - Education: Economic Education Council, 1973; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Meetings/Box12:27 (Box-folder 12:27)
      - Education: 1976 Education Series Speakers, 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Meetings/Box12:28 (Box-folder 12:28)
      - Education: Education Series Planning, 1976; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Meetings/Box12:29 (Box-folder 12:29)
      - Energy, undated; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box13:1 (Box-folder 13:1)
      - Field meetings: Subcommittee on Field Work, 1957-1959; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box13:2 (Box-folder 13:2)
      - Field Meetings, 1953; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box13:3 (Box-folder 13:3)
      - Field Meetings, 1957; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box13:4 (Box-folder 13:4)
      - Field meetings, 1960; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box13:5 (Box-folder 13:5)
      - Field Meetings: 1970 Madison, 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box13:6 (Box-folder 13:6)
      - Field Meetings: 1970 Danbury, 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box13:7 (Box-folder 13:7)
      - Field Meetings: 1970 Fairfield, 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box13:8 (Box-folder 13:8)
      - Foreign students: Foreign Student Forum, 1952 (Box-folder 13:9)
      - Foreign Students: Auerfarm Meeting, 1962 (Box-folder 13:10)
      - Foreign Students: Foreign Student Weekend, 1959 (Box-folder 13:11)
      - Foreign Students: International Student Weekend, 1970 (Box-folder 13:12)
      - Foreign Students: Directories 1957, 1959, 1962, 1963, 1957-1963 (Box-folder 13:13)
      - Foreign Students: Directories 1967-1969, 1973, 1967-1973 (Box-folder 13:14)
      - Foreign Students: Directories 1974-1975 (Box-folder 13:15)
      - Forums: American issues Forum, undated; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box13:16 (Box-folder 13:16)
      - Forums: Fall Forum 1970, 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box13:17 (Box-folder 13:17)
      - Group homes, undated (Box 14, Folder 323)
      - Guests of B. Auerbach, 1945-1964 (Box 14, Folder 324-331)
      - International issues, 1945-1976 (Box 14, Folder 332-338)
      - International Women's Year Awards, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 339)
      - Lane Bryant Annual Awards, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 340)
      - Libraries, 1952, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 341-342)
      - Organizational techniques, 1945-1964 (Box 14, Folder 343)
      - Picnics, 1970-1974 (Box 14, Folder 344)
      - Press party, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 345)
      - Procedures, 1945-1975 (Box 14, Folder 346)
      - Publicity, 1945-1976 (Box 14, Folder 347-357)
      - Regional Conference, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 358)
      - Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1949-1951 (Box 14, Folder 359)
      - Seminars, 1966-1972 (Box 14, Folder 360-363)
      - United Nations Week, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 364)
      - Volunteers (Auerfarm), 1966 (Box 14, Folder 365)
    - Projects
      - Carrie Chapman Catt Fund, Report on German Project, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 366)
      - Juvenile Justice [also see Series VII] (Box 14, Folder 367)
      - Law related education, 1978-1981 (Box 14, Folder 368-369)
      - "Projects in your program", 1956 (Box 15:, Folder 370)
    - Scholarships, 1951-1961 (Box 15:, Folder 371)
    - Trips, undated (Box 15:, Folder 372-381)
  - Subseries E: Foreign Visitors, undated, 1947-1976
    - Sample file, language list, 1973-1976 (Box 15:, Folder 382)
    - Women's organizations abroad, undated (Box 15:, Folder 383)
    - 1947-1948 (Box 15:, Folder 384)
    - 1949 (Box 15:, Folder 385-388)
    - 1949-1951 (Box 15:, Folder 389)
    - 1950 (Box 15:, Folder 390)
    - 1951 (Box 15:, Folder 391)
    - 1952 (Box 15:, Folder 392-393)
    - 1953 (Box 15:, Folder 394)
    - 1954 (Box 15:, Folder 395-397)
    - 1955 (Box 15:, Folder 398-400)
    - 1956 (Box 15:, Folder 401-404)
    - 1957 (Box 15:, Folder 405-407)
    - 1958 (Box 16:, Folder 408-410)
    - 1959 (Box 16:, Folder 411-413)
    - 1960 (Box 16:, Folder 414-416)
    - 1961 (Box 16:, Folder 417-419)
    - 1962 (Box 16:, Folder 420-422)
    - 1963 (Box 16:, Folder 423-428)
    - 1964 (Box 16:, Folder 429-433)
    - 1964 (Box 17:, Folder 434-436)
    - 1965 (Box 17:, Folder 437-442)
  - Subseries F: Photographs, undated
    - Photographs, undated (Box 17:, Folder 443-455)
  - Subseries G: Newsclipping Scrapbooks, 1944-1976
    - 1944-1954 (Box 18)
    - 1954-1957 (Box 19)
    - 1958-1962 (Box 20)
    - 1963-1968 (Box 21)
    - 1969-1976 (Box 22)
  - Subseries H: Meeting Attendance Books, 1947-1955
    - Guest Book, 1947-1955 (Box 23:, Folder 456)
    - Meeting lists, 1946-1954 (Box 1:, Folder 457-458)
    - Meeting lists, 1954-1955 (Box 24:, Folder 459)
- Series III: Trends in Occupations Project, undated, 1900-1953
  - Subseries A: Tables [Bound as listed below, some may have multiple volumes], undated
    - Population (Box 24:, Folder 1-11)
    - Agriculture (Box 24:, Folder 12-14)
    - Forestry and Fishing (Box 24:, Folder 15-17)
    - Extraction of minerals (Box 24:, Folder 18-20)
    - Manufacturing and mechanical industries, skilled operatives (Box 24:, Folder 21-22)
    - Manufacturing and mechanical industries, semi-skilled operatives (Box 24:, Folder 23)
    - Manufacturing and mechanical industries, laborers (Box 24:, Folder 24)
    - Manufacturing and mechanical industries, skilled operators (Box 24:, Folder 25)
    - Manufacturing and mechanical industries, semi-skilled operatives (Box 24:, Folder 26)
    - Manufacturing and mechanical industries, laborers (Box 24:, Folder 27)
    - Transportation and communication (Box 24:, Folder 28-30)
    - Trade (Box 24:, Folder 31-33)
    - Public service (not elsewhere classified) (Box 24:, Folder 34-36)
    - Professional service (Box 24:, Folder 37-38)
    - Professional service (Box 24:, Folder 39)
    - Domestic and personal service (Box 24:, Folder 40-41)
    - Domestic and personal service (Box 24:, Folder 42)
    - Clerical occupations (Box 24:, Folder 43-45)
    - Males in selected occupations (Box 24:, Folder 46-48)
    - Females in selected occupations—age and marital status in 1920 (Box 24:, Folder 49-50)
    - Females in selected occupations—age and marital status in 1930 (Box 24:, Folder 51-52)
    - Age distribution of all women and of married women 1920-1930 (Box 24:, Folder 53)
    - Gainfully occupied married women—age, color and nativity 1920-1930 (Box 24:, Folder 54)
  - Subseries B: Reports, undated, 1900-1937
    - Cumulative report on project 2085, formerly 990, 1936 (Box 25:, Folder 460)
    - Occupations in the United States and the South, 1910-1930. Connecticut WPA 2085, Trends in Occupations (1st draft), 1937 (Box 25:, Folder 461-462)
    - Occupations in the United States and the South, 1910-1930. Connecticut WPA 2085, Trends in Occupations (1st draft, annotated), 1937 (Box 25:, Folder 463)
    - Occupations in the United States and the South, 1910-1930. Connecticut WPA 2085, Trends in Occupations (1st draft, Section II), 1937 (Box 25:, Folder 464)
    - Footnotes—selected occupations females 1920, undated (Box 25:, Folder 465)
    - Trends in occupations—lists of tables, 1937 (Box 25:, Folder 466)
    - Trends in women's work 1910-1930, 1936 (Box 25:, Folder 467)
  - Subseries C: Reference Files, undated, 1900-1953
    - Bibliographies, undated (Box 25:, Folder 468)
    - Connecticut Social trends, CT Emergency Relief Commission, v. 1, #1-v. 2, #1, 1935-1936 (Box 25:, Folder 469-470)
    - Employment, 1937 (Box 25:, Folder 471)
    - Occupational Trends
      - Age, undated (Box 25:, Folder 472)
        - Notes, 1932-1937 (Box 25:, Folder 473)
        - Publications, 1929-1940 (Box 25:, Folder 474)
    - Migration
      - Notes, undated (Box 25:, Folder 475)
      - Publications, undated (Box 25:, Folder 476)
    - Occupations
      - Notes, undated (Box 25:, Folder 477)
      - Bureau of census data, undated (Box 25:, Folder 478)
      - Publications, undated (Box 25:, Folder 479)
      - Classifications, undated (Box 25:, Folder 480)
      - Government service, undated (Box 25:, Folder 481)
      - Guidance, undated (Box 25:, Folder 482)
      - Manufacturing and mechanical industries notes, undated (Box 26:, Folder 483-484)
      - Medicine—publications, undated (Box 26:, Folder 485-486)
      - Service occupations, undated (Box 26:, Folder 487)
      - Technology, undated (Box 26:, Folder 488)
      - Textiles and clothing, undated (Box 26:, Folder 489)
      - Transportation and communication, undated (Box 26:, Folder 490)
    - Relief studies, 1934-1936 (Box 26:, Folder 491)
    - Shortages (labor)—notes, undated (Box 26:, Folder 492)
    - States and cities (1900 occupation by sex), undated (Box 26:, Folder 493)
    - Southern regions, undated (Box 26:, Folder 494)
    - Women
      - Employment, undated (Box 26:, Folder 495)
      - Equal pay, undated (Box 26:, Folder 496)
      - Law, undated (Box 26:, Folder 497)
      - Marriage, undated (Box 26:, Folder 498)
      - Married Women
        - Employed, undated (Box 26:, Folder 499)
        - Family, undated (Box 26:, Folder 500)
        - Work, undated (Box 26:, Folder 501)
      - Property rights, undated (Box 26:, Folder 502)
      - War, undated (Box 26:, Folder 503)
      - Work, undated (Box 26:, Folder 504)
    - Population trends (Box not specified)
      - Notes—trends, undated (Box 27:, Folder 505)
      - Notes—statistics, undated (Box 27:, Folder 506)
      - Publications, undated (Box 27:, Folder 507-509)
      - Bureau of Census Publications
        - Census report, 1930 (Box 27:, Folder 510-511)
        - Census, 1940 (Box 27:, Folder 512)
        - Releases, 1930-1947 (Box 27:, Folder 513-515)
    - Standard of living
      - American—general, 1930-1935 (Box 27:, Folder 516)
      - Barnard College Alumni income, 1929 (Box 27:, Folder 517)
      - Budgets, undated (Box 27:, Folder 518)
        - Making a budget, undated (Box 27:, Folder 519)
        - Savings and insurance, undated (Box 27:, Folder 520)
        - Suggested budget, undated (Box 27:, Folder 521)
      - Consumer demand, undated (Box 27:, Folder 522)
      - Consumption, undated (Box 27:, Folder 523)
      - Economic organization in household, undated (Box 27:, Folder 524)
      - Expenditure theory, undated (Box 28:, Folder 525)
      - Family expenditures, undated (Box 1:, Folder 526)
      - Family expenditures: tables, undated (Box 1:, Folder 527)
      - Family Expenditures: data tables, undated (Box 1:, Folder 528)
      - Family: dependent, undated (Box 1:, Folder 529)
      - Farms
        - General, undated (Box 1:, Folder 530)
        - Equipment, undated (Box 1:, Folder 531)
        - Family, undated (Box 1:, Folder 532)
        - Furnished/home equipment, undated (Box 1:, Folder 533)
      - Foreign, undated (Box 1:, Folder 534)
      - Household management, undated (Box 1:, Folder 535)
      - Housing, undated (Box 1:, Folder 536)
      - Income data, undated (Box 1:, Folder 537)
      - Individuals, undated (Box 1:, Folder 538)
      - Installment buying, undated (Box 1:, Folder 539)
      - Leisure, undated (Box 1:, Folder 540)
      - Price index, consumer inflation, undated (Box 1:, Folder 541)
      - Price trends, early 19th century, undated (Box 1:, Folder 542)
      - Professional, undated (Box 1:, Folder 543-544)
      - Unemployment, undated (Box 1:, Folder 545)
      - Women's Bureau (Department of Labor), undated (Box 1:, Folder 546)
    - Tables
      - Farm families accounts, undated (Box 29:, Folder 547)
      - Farm families schedules, undated (Box 29:, Folder 548)
      - Urban families standard of living, undated (Box 29:, Folder 549)
      - City families summary sheets, undated (Box 29:, Folder 550)
      - Farm families, Maryland and Illinois, undated (Box 29:, Folder 551)
      - Farm families, Vermont, undated (Box 29:, Folder 552)
      - City families accounts and schedules, undated (Box 29:, Folder 553)
      - Massachusetts totals for towns between 10,000 and 75,000 people, undated (Box 29:, Folder 554)
      - Standard deviations for accounts and schedules, not used, undated (Box 29:, Folder 555)
      - Analytical tables: Professional service, undated (Box 29:, Folder 556-560)
      - Analytical tables: Professional service II, undated (Box 29:, Folder 561-562)
      - Analytical tables: Professional service III, undated (Box 29:, Folder 563-564)
      - Analytical tables: Professional service file 3, undated (Box 29:, Folder 565)
      - Analytical tables: Professional service file 4, undated (Box 29:, Folder 566)
      - Occupations, Professional services, 1900-1920 (Box 29:, Folder 567)
      - Professional services totals, 1900-1920 (Box 29:, Folder 568)
      - Professional services, cross-checking sheets, undated (Box 29:, Folder 569)
      - Tables for streetcleaners and owners and managers of truck transfer, cab companies, undated (Box 29:, Folder 570)
- Series IV: Status of Women, undated, 1908-1981
  - Correspondence
    - Governor's Committee on the Status of Women, 1965-1979 (Box 30:, Folder 571-576)
  - Subseries A: Organizations and Publications, undated, 1923-1981
    - Alert, 1972-1976 (Box 30:, Folder 577-578)
    - Alicia Patterson Foundation, 1971-1974 (Box 30:, Folder 579)
    - Altrusa International, 1941 (Box 30:, Folder 580)
    - American Association of University Women (AAUW), 1935-1973 (Box 30:, Folder 581)
    - American Nursing Society, 1966 (Box 30:, Folder 582)
    - Book of the States, 1968-1969 (Box 30:, Folder 583)
    - Booklets published by the Government Printing Office, 1931-1962 (Box 30:, Folder 584-585)
    - Breakthrough, 1971-1977 (Box 30:, Folder 586)
    - Bulletin, 1967 (Box 30:, Folder 587)
    - Business and Professional Women's Foundation, 1969 (Box 30:, Folder 588)
    - Catalyst, 1969-1970 (Box 30:, Folder 589)
    - Catholic Woman, 1975 (Box 30:, Folder 590)
    - Center for Continuing Education of Women, 1972-1979 (Box 30:, Folder 591)
    - Citizen's Advisory Council on the Status of Women, Washington, D.C., 1963-1978 (Box 30:, Folder 592-598)
    - Citizen's Advisory Council on the Status of Women, Wisconsin, 1967-1970 (Box 31:, Folder 599)
    - Civil Service Commission, 1969 (Box 31:, Folder 600)
    - Colleges and Universities
      - Barnard, 1928, 1935 (Box 31:, Folder 601)
      - Boston University, 1935 (Box 31:, Folder 602)
      - University of Pennsylvania, 1928-1976
      - University of Connecticut, 1962-1981 (Box 31:, Folder 603)
      - University of Michigan, 1930, 1967-70 (Box 31:, Folder 604-605)
      - University of Minnesota, 1962-1965 (Box 31:, Folder 606)
      - Stanford University, 1926-1932
      - Sarah Lawrence College, 1956-1966 (Box 31:, Folder 607)
      - University of Wisconsin, 1963-1973 (Box 31:, Folder 608)
      - Yale University, 1970 (Box 31:, Folder 609)
      - Goddard College, 1963-1965 (Box 31:, Folder 610)
      - Smith College, 1923-1924 (Box 31:, Folder 611)
      - Sarah Lawrence College, 1962-1964
      - Alabama College, 1924, 1936
      - University of Kansas City, 1963 (Box 31:, Folder 612)
      - University of Chicago, 1965-1966
      - New York University, 1964 (Box 31:, Folder 613)
      - Oakland University, 1966-1967
      - Vassar College, 1960, 1962 (Box 31:, Folder 614)
      - Columbia University, 1963, 1967
      - Washington University, 1968 (Box 31:, Folder 615)
      - Radcliffe College, 1960-1967
      - Goucher College, 1928 (Box 31:, Folder 616)
      - Wesleyan University, 1970
      - Woman's College of the University of North Carolina, 1933 (Box 31:, Folder 617)
      - Loretto Heights College, 1968 (Box 31:, Folder 618)
      - Syracuse University, New York University and New School for Social Research, 1964-1965 (Box 31:, Folder 619)
    - College Quarterlies
      - Radcliffe College, 1968 (Box 31:, Folder 620)
      - Goucher College, 1924 (Box 31:, Folder 621)
      - Mortar Board, 1933, 1938 (Box 31:, Folder 622)
      - Hollins College, 1935 (Box 31:, Folder 623)
      - University of Pennsylvania, 1939 (Box 31:, Folder 624)
    - Commission on Organizations of the Executive Branch of Government, 1949 (Box 31:, Folder 625)
    - Common Cause, 1972 (Box 31:, Folder 626)
    - Congressional Record, 1945-1977 (Box 31:, Folder 627)
    - Connecticut Commission on Civil Rights, 1967
    - Connecticut Commission on the Status of Women, 1966-1967
    - Connecticut Conference of Municipalities, 1974-1975
    - Connecticut Conference on the Status of Women, 1972
    - Connecticut/Difference Organization, undated
    - Connecticut Directory of Consumer Resources, 1970 (Box 32)
    - Connecticut General Assembly State Capital, 1973
    - Connecticut, Governor's Committee on the Status of Women, 1967-1977
    - Connecticut Health Services, 1970-1975
    - Connecticut issues and opportunities, 1970
    - Connecticut League of Women Voters, 1967
    - Connecticut Permanent Commission on the Status of Women, 1967-1980 (Box 32:, Folder 2 fl)
    - Connecticut Planned Parenthood League of Greater Hartford, 1947
    - Connecticut Public Television, 1975
    - Connecticut Regional Medical Program (CRMP), 1973, 1975
    - Connecticut, 1962-1981 (Box 32:, Folder 4 fl)
    - Connecticut Valley Conference on Employment Problems Of Women, 1962
    - Connecticut Women's Political Caucus, 1974-1980
    - Connecticut/Southeastern Connecticut Regional Planning, 1977
    - Delta Kappa Gamma, 1964-1977 (Box 32:, Folder 2 fl)
    - Democratic National Committee, 1969
    - >Department of Commerce, 1940, 1950
    - Department of Health, 1946, 1970, 1972
    - Department of Labor, Connecticut, 1966
    - Department of Labor, U.S., 1938-1978 (Box 32:, Folder 2 fl)
    - Department of Labor, U.S., 1938-1978 (Box 33:, Folder 8 fl)
    - Department of Labor News, 1962-1973
    - Enlace, 1967-1976
    - Equal Rights, 1943-1946
    - Federal Council on Art Education and Institute of Women's Professional Relations, 1935-1936
    - Ford Foundation, 1972-1975
    - Governor's Committee on the Status of Women, various States, undated
    - Harper's Monthly Magazine, undated
    - Hartford Interval House, Inc., 1980
    - Home Economics and Family Studies, University of CT, undated
    - Impact, 1976
    - Information and Counseling Services for Women, 1973
    - Institute of Women's Professional Relations, 1930-1941
    - Inter-American Commission of Women, 1954-1976 (Box 33:, Folder 3 fl)
    - International Assembly of Women, 1946 (Box 34)
    - International Forum on the Role of Women in Population And Development, 1974-1975
    - International Women's Conference, 1950
    - International Women's Year, 1975-1978 (Box 34:, Folder 3 fl)
    - Interstate Association of Commissions on the Status of Women, 1970-1975
    - "IoWoman", 1972
    - McCall's Magazine, undated
    - Media Report to Women, undated
    - Midwest Regional Newsletter on the Status of Women, 1969
    - MP Guidelines, 1964-1968
    - National Association of Commission on the Status of Women (NACSW), 1975
    - National Association of Deans of Women, 1955
    - National Association for Executive Females, Inc., undated
    - National Citizens' Commission, 1965
    - National Commission on Working Women (NCWW), 1979
    - National Committee to Defeat the Un-Equal Rights Amendment, 1944-1968
    - National Council of Administrative Women in Education, 1965
    - National Council of Jewish Women (NCJW), 1979
    - National Council of Women of the United States, Inc., undated
    - National League of Women Voters, 1924-1944
    - National Organization for Women (NOW) [Includes Hite's Feminist Sexuality Questionnaire], 1966-1976
    - National Women's Committee for Civil Rights, 1963-1964
    - National Woman's Conference, 1957-1977